A Guide to the F. Claiborne Johnston, Jr. Papers, 1904-2010
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
F. Claiborne Johnston, Jr. Papers, 1904-2010
The Library of Virginia
51830
12.4 cubic feet (28 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of F. Claiborne Johnston, Jr., Richmond.
Biographical Information
Francis Claiborne (Jay) Johnston, Jr. was born in Richmond, Virginia on 6 January 1943. He is the son of Francis Claiborne Johnston, Sr. (1903-1981) and Virginia Maupin Williams (1906-1992). He graduated from Princeton University in 1964, and earned his law degree from the University of Virginia in 1967. Johnston married Carolyn Hooper Satterfield on 5 December 1970. She is the daughter of John Angier Satterfield (1914-2008) and Carolyn Branson Hooper (1925-2008). They live in Richmond, where he practiced law. He also has served on the boards of the Library of Virginia, Westminster-Canterbury Corporation, and The Valentine.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1904-2010, of F. Claiborne Johnston, Jr. of Richmond, Virginia, containing biographical, genealogical, and historical research for various articles, books, and sketches he published between 1987 and 2010. The collection includes abstracts, copies, and transcriptions of census records, chancery records, deeds, land patents and grants, military and pension records, tax records, tombstone inscriptions, vital statistics, and wills and estate administration records. There are also clippings, correspondence with other researchers, compiled genealogies and research by other individuals, drafts and endnotes of his works, genealogical charts, maps, newsletters, obituaries, original family papers, photographs, and published articles and book extracts by others.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I. The Williams/Sims Families of Greene/Orange Counties, Virginia (1987).
II. The Pinder/Ellett Families of Virginia and Georgia and Allied Families (1988).
III. Satterfield and Allied Families of Person County, North Carolina and Surrounding Counties (1992).
IV. The Angier Family of Orange and Durham Counties, North Carolina (1995).
V. Sketches for the Dictionary of Virginia Biography (2001).
VI. The Hoopers of Caswell and Durham Counties, North Carolina and Allied Families, With Their Virginia Origins (2002).
VII. The Tangled Trail of Two John Popes (2010).
VIII. The Tangled Trail of Benjamin Dawson of Orange and Spotsylvania Counties, and the City of Richmond and Northumberland, Fauquier and Frederick Counties in Virginia (2010).
Contents List
- Series I. The Williams/Sims Families of Greene/Orange Counties, Virginia (1987)., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 1-3)
  The Williams/Sims Families of Greene/Orange Counties, Virginia and Allied Families (Riddle, Powell, McMullan, Walker, Maupin, Banks, Miller, and Beadles) contains information related to Johnston's maternal line. His goal was to trace the Williams and Sims and related family lines as far as possible in America. It includes detailed studies of Orange County court records using published abstracts by others, especially John Frederick Dorman III and Sam and Ruth Sparacio. Johnston also relied heavily upon the work of other researchers who have studied the McMullan, Maupin, Miller, and Powell families.
  - Beadles/Miller/Maupin. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Descendants of James Beazley (d. 1803). (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beazley-Sims-Jarrell Family Bible Record (Other Data). (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Catterton/Ansell (Ancell). (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chancery Records - Orange and Greene Counties VA. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Durrett. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ham/Hamm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Harvey. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Herring/Herrin. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Herring/Stodgill. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Kendall. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Land Patents - Orange and Spotsylvania Counties VA. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Daniel Mackgirt/Mackgurt/Magirt. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Maupin. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Maupin/Via. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - McMullen. (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Neal/Neale. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Orange and Greene Counties VA. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Pemberton. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Pemberton/Maxwell. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Penn/Burruss/Tandy/Callaway. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Powell. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Honorias Powell. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Descendants of John and Ann Powell (Culpeper County VA). (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Riddle/Riddell. (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Rogers. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Shifflett. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sims - Hanover and Louisa Counties VA. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - John Sims (Son of William). (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Snow/Shiflets/Roach. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Stodghill. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Towles/Kendall. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Wait/Wayt. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Watts. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Series II. The Pinder/Ellett Families of Virginia and Georgia and Allied Families (1988)., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 3-6)
  The Pinder/Ellett Families of Virginia and Georgia and Allied Families (Pinder, Tebeau, Treutlen, Ellett, Spears, Womack, Sublett, Cheatham, Smith, Trabue) With Some Account of the Pinder/Pindar Family Trail in the Bahama Islands, Bermuda, and Barbados begins with the story of Joseph William Pinder family of Savannah and its Georgia progeny. Johnston then retraces the family backward in time. Succeeding chapters cover the Ellett lines, and then the family of Joseph William Pinder (1828-1897) by his two marriages. Again, his goal was to track all lines as far back in America as possible. The impetus for this volume was the original family papers that were handed down to him by his mother, and research by his aunt, Belle Pinder Rand. There are also bibliographies, guides to library and archival holdings, research aids, and histories of the Bahama Islands, Bermuda, and Barbados, as well as information on the Bahamas DNA Project.
  - Bahamas DNA Project. (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
  - Bahamas - Department of Archives Info/Holdings. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bahamas - Email re: Genealogy. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bahamas - Miscellaneous Records. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bahamas - P.R.O. Guide to Records. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bahamas - Research Aids/LDS Library Listings. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bahamas - Wills. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Laurie Baker Materials. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bermuda - History, Books, Articles. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bibliography of Bahamian Genealogy/Eric Whittleton Article. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Births and Baptistms - Harbour Island Church Register. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Birth and Marriage Records (Peggy Glass). (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Caribbean Research/Vera L. Oliver. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Eleuthera. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Peggy Glass Materials. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Grymesditch. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Jeffrey L. Haines. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hutchins. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Leaycraft. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Loyalists in the Bahama Islands (Thelma Peters). (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Monroe County FL Library - Bahama Holdings/Pinders of Florida. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Monumental Inscriptions of the British West Indies by Vere Langford Oliver. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - National Archives (U.K.). (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Pinder. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Pinder - Bahamas. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Pinder/Pindar - Barbados. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Pinder - Charleston and Georgia Historical Societies. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Pinder Charts. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - The Pinder/Ellett Families of Virginia and Georgia and Allied Families (Pinder, Tebeau, Treutlen, Ellett, Spears, Womack, Sublett, Cheatham, Smith, Trabue) With Some Account of the Pinder/Pindar Family Trail in the Bahama Islands, Bermuda, and Barbados. (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Pinder - English Connections. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pinder - English Records. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pinder - Jamaica Research. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Pinder Family Materials - Bermuda. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Pinder/Hutchins - Georgia and South Carolina Records. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Pinder Marriages. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Pinder - North Carolina. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pinder - South Carolina. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Pinder, Richard (1634?-1695). (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
  - Pinder, Ridley. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Pinder - Savannah - New Material. (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Pinder - Wills - Bahamas. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Public Record Office Sources. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Quaker Materials. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Research Guides, Sources, etc. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Ridley/Cheeseman/Snipes/Morris. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Stiles/Pierce/Smith/Massie. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Vesey/Estlak. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Web Materials - Bermuda/Barbados/Caribbean. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Series III. Satterfield and Allied Families of Person County, North Carolina and Surrounding Counties (1992)., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 7-10)
  Satterfield and Allied Families of Person County, North Carolina (Yarbrough, Carter, Bigger, Cary, Winstead, Cozart, Bumpass, Sargent, Gold, Carney, Walker, and Davey Families) contains research on Johnston's wife's ancestors. Beginning with her parents, Johnston attempted to trace back all lines in America, but soon limited it to her paternal line, with a focus on Person, Caswell, and Orange Counties, North Carolina. This series also includes a copy of an article Johnston wrote for the Bulletin of The Genealogical Society of Old Tryon County in 2008 entitled "Rethinking the Ancestry of Daniel Gold (? - 1793) of Mecklenburg County, Virginia."
  - Bumpass Family Origins. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Daniel Danielson. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Dollar (Princess Anne/Norfolk). (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Foster. (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
  - Foster, John (Perkins/Fergusson/Farguson). (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "Descendants of Daniel and Elizabeth Pleasant Gold" by Joe Gold. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Descendants of John Gold the Crusader. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Gold (Eastern North Carolina). (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Gold (FamilySearch Records). (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Gold (Granville District, Anson and Orange Counties NC). (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Gold (Lunenburg and Mecklenburg Counties VA). (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Gold (Maryland). (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - Gold (Miscellaneous Research Notes). (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Gold (Northern Virginia). (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Gold (Surry, Isle of Wight, Elizabeth City Counties VA). (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gold Generations in England and America by Pleasant Daniel Gold. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Harrelson/Walker. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Horton, Hugh Jr. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Horton, John Wilson. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Horton, Thomas. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Horton/Kenrick/Wilson. (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
  - Horton/Whorton - Westmoreland and Stafford Counties VA. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Jay. (Box 8, Folder 16-17)
  - Kimbro/Kimbrough/Jones (Caswell County). (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Kimbrough. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Kimbrough/Miles/Shelton/Matlock/McComas/Graves. (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Land Patents, Minutes, etc. - North Carolina. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Lyon/Pulliam. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Mecklenburg County VA 1850 Census (22nd District). (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Mecklenburg County VA 1850 Census (98th District). (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Owen - Joe Gold Inquiry. (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
  - Perkins-Ferguson/Farguson. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "Rethinking the Ancestry of Daniel Gold (? - 1793) of Mecklenburg County Virginia." (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - Salling/Salley/Carter/Bickley. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Salling II. (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Descendants of William Sargent, Sr. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Satterfield. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Satterfield Materials Found After 1992. (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - Satterfield Family Association. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Satterfield, James - Land Grants (Rutherford County NC). (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Southwest Virginia. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Strong/Fields/Gibson/Webster. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Wilson/Willson-Lawson. (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
  - Yancey. (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Series IV. The Angier Family of Orange and Durham Counties, North Carolina (1995)., Extent: 6 boxes. (Box 11-16)
  The Angier Family of Orange and Durham Counties, North Carolina, and Allied Families of North Carolina and Virginia (Dollar, Pearson, Trice, Duke, Jones, Yancey, and Withers) traces the maternal line of Johnston's wife's father back nine generations in America. It includes a good deal of information on the Duke family, some taken from records of the Duke Family Association. Much of Johnston's research was taken from work previously done by William D. Bennett, Weynette Haun, Brent Holcomb, and Ruth Shields.
  - William Ager/Agur (ca. 1610-1654) - Salem MA. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Anger/Angers - Louisiana. (Box 11, Folder 2-5)
  - John Anger/Hannah Aspinwall. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Angier - England/New England. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Angier Family Bible Records. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Angier (NC/VA/SC/MD). (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Angier - Other. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - John Angier (1744-1833). (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - John Angier (1744-1833) - New York State. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - John C. Angier. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Joseph Angier. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Lida Duke Angier. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Malbourn A. Angier. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Matthew Angier/ M.A. Angier (NC). (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Matthew B. Angier - Mobile County AL. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Oakes Angier. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Samuel T. Angier. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Angier/Duke - Corrected Pages. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Angier/Duke - Obituaries, Clippings. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Angier-Parmelee Bible Record. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Carrington/Mangum/Parker. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Carter/Bigger/Waddill/Crew. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cozart/Cozzart/Bumpass. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Deeds (Orange and Caswell Counties NC). (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dollar/Rhodes. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Duke. (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
  - Duke Family Association. (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Duke/Jones/Dicey/Moses (Orange and Person Counties NC). (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Genealogical Charts. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Gilmore/Heard. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Halstead, Marilyn. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hemenway/Parmalee. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Hooper. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Moses Jones/William Jones (Granville County NC). (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
  - Maps and Brochures - New York. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Pearson/Gilmore/Simmons/Thurston. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Photographs. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Sargent/Carney/Gold/Lea/Seat. (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
  - Abraham Sargeant. (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Abraham/Abram Sargeant - Knox and Harlan Counties KY. (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - Abraham/Abram Sargeant - Others. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Nancy Sargeant/William Morgan. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stephen Sargeant/Margaret Gold. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - William Sargeant - Orange County NC. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Satterfield. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Carlotta Gilmore Angier Satterfield. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Henry C. Satterfield. Sr. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - John A. Satterfield. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Satterfield - Other. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Trice/Daniel. (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Trice (Daniel/Patterson). (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Walker/Davy (Davie). (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Moses Walker (d. 1806 Person County NC)/Robert Walker (d.1767 Bedford County VA). (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
  - Winstead. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Winstead/Winston. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Yancey/Withers/Ashby/Mitchell/Turner/Keene/Powers. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Yarborough. (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Series V. Sketches for the Dictionary of Virginia Biography (2001)., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 16-18)
  This series contains research materials related to biographical sketches Johnston contributed to the Dictionary of Virginia Biography on George Carrington (1758-1809) and Thomas Carter (1731-1803). There is also a good deal of information on Johnston's investigation into the location of Carrington's estate, "Oak Hill" in Halifax County.
  - Carrington, George (1758-1809). (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
  - Carrington, George - Bible of Paul Carrington (Transcripts). (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Carrington, George - Carrington/Coles Genealogy. (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Carrington, George - DVB Agreement, Guidelines, etc. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Carrington, George - Draft of DVB Sketch. (Box 16, Folder 9-12)
  - Carrington, George - Handwriting Samples. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Carrington, George - Homes ("Elmwood"/"Oak Hill". (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Carrington, George - Kentucky Lands. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Carrington, George - Land Records. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Carrington, George - Marriage Records. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Carrington, George - Military Service/Land Grant. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Carrington, George - Notes by Mary Watkins Leigh Taliaferro. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Carrington, George - "Oak Hill" - Deeds. (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
  - Carrington, George - "Oak Hill" - Essay. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Carrington, George - "Oak Hill" - Maps and Plats. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Carrington, George - "Oak Hill" - Photographs. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Carrington, George - Obituary. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Carrington, George - Ohio Lands. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Carrington, George - Research/Checklists. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Carrington, George - Society of the Cincinnati. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Carrington, George - Will and Inventory. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Carter, Thomas (1731-1803). (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Carter, Thomas - Biographical Sketches. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Carter, Thomas - Burial. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Carter, Thomas - Chancery Suit Papers. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Carter, Thomas - Draft of DVB Sketch. (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - Carter, Thomas - Land Records. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Carter, Thomas - Legislative/Public Service. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Carter, Thomas - Letters to Governor re: Indian Attacks/Threats. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Carter, Thomas - Map (Russell and Scott Counties VA). (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Carter, Thomas - Marriages. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Carter, Thomas - Militia. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Carter, Thomas - Prayer Book (VHS). (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Carter, Thomas - Will and Inventory. (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Series VI.The Hoopers of Caswell and Durham Counties, North Carolina and Allied Families, With Their Virginia Origins (2002)., Extent: 6 boxes. (Box 18-23)
  The Hoopers of Caswell and Durham County, North Carolina and Allied Families, With Their Virginia Origins (Walker, Henderson, Kimbrough/Kimbro, Jones, Foster, Horton, Wilson/Willson, Strong, Salling and Carter) traces Johnston's wife's maternal line. There is detailed information on the Hooper line in Caswell County that leads back to Zachariah Hooper of Amelia County, Virignia, and other Hooper lines in Virginia. There is also research on the paternal line of Capt. Richard Jones (ca. 1784-1861) of Caswell County, much of it with the aid of Audrey Z. Jones of Lexington, Kentucky. There is a good deal of correspondence with her, as well as Marilyn Symonds. The work of Katherine Kerr Kendall in abstracting Caswell County records, and information on the Hooper family provided by D. Wayne Gunn of Kingsville, Texas was also used to compile this volume. There are also copies of the Hooper Compass newsletter.
  - Robert and Martha Alexander/Robert Munford. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Baptist Ministers and Churches/William Creath. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Capt. John Batte (1606-1653). (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Burwell - Mecklenburg County VA. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1992-2007. (Box 19, Folder 1-9)
  - Anne Goodwin. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Drewey Wayne Gunn. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Mary Hooper Gunn. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Hooper - Census. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Hooper Compass (Volume 1). (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Hooper Compass (Volumes 2-6). (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
  - Hooper - Military Records. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Hooper - Other (VA/NC/MD). (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "Third" Hooper Family of Caswell County. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Hooper/Woodliffe/Henderson. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Connie Hooper. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Darrow Hooper. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - George Hooper Descendants (Goochland, Cumberland, Buckingham Counties VA). (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Descendants of Col. George Hooper by Marilyn Hooper Symonds. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - John Calvin Hooper. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Descendants of Obediah and Massilva Brooks Hooper. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Rufus J. Hooper. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Hooper/Innis Hooper. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - William Hooper the Signer. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Zachariah Hooper Bible Record. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Zachariah L. Hooper. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Bunny Hooper Horton. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Jones - Amelia County VA. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Jones - Brunswick and Lunenburg Counties VA. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Jones - Charts, etc. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Jones - Dinwiddie County VA. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Jones Families of Virginia. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Jones Family Histories. (Box 21, Folder 12-14)
  - Jones Family History by Nannie Matilda Pleasant. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Jones - Halifax County VA. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Jones - Mecklenburg County Chancery Causes. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Jones - Mecklenburg County Deeds and Wills. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Jones - Mecklenburg County Tax Records. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Jones - North Carolina. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Jones - Northampton County NC. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Jones - Northumberland County VA/Granville County NC. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Jones - Nottoway County VA/Capt. Richard Jones - Pittsylvania County VA. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Jones - Plats (Marilyn Symonds). (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jones - Richmond County VA. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Descendants of Abraham Wood Jones by Marilyn Hooper Symonds. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Audrey Jones/Marilyn Symonds. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Audrey Jones Materials. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Edward M. Jones. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Capt. Peter Jones (Brunswick/Dinwiddie). (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Descendants of Peter Jones I of Charles City County, Virginia by Marilyn Hooper Symonds. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Descendants of Margaret and 1) Peter Jones I and 2) Thomas Cocke by Marilyn Hooper Symonds. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Peter Jones - Charlotte County. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Richard Jones - Caswell County NC. (Box 22, Folder 18)